<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<templates xml:space="preserve">
    <t t-name="owlybook.OwlybookView" owl="1">
        <MainComponentsContainer/>
        <div class="d-sm-flex flex-row h-100 bg-white">
            <Sidebar t-if="!hideSidebar" stories="stories.stories"/>
            <div class="d-flex flex-column bg-white w-100 h-100 position-relative" style="width:100px">
                <div t-if="!hideSidebar" class="o_owlybook_topbar text-black w-100">
                    <div class="d-flex flex-row justify-content-between border-bottom align-items-center">
                        <span class="p-3">
                            <t t-esc="stories.active.title"/>
                            <t t-if="stories.active.title">
                                <i t-if="!stories.active.arch" class="fa fa-code ms-2"/>
                            </t>
                        </span>

                    </div>
                </div>

                <t t-if="stories.active.title">
                    <Canvas/>
                    <Panel t-key="stories.active.id"/>
                </t>
                <t t-else="">
                   <t t-call="owlybook.Introduction"/>
                </t>
            </div>
        </div>
    </t>

    <t t-name="owlybook.Introduction" owl="1">
        <div class="m-5 p-5">
            <h1><strong>Welcome to Owlybook ! 👋 🦉 </strong></h1><br/>
            <h2><font class="text-o-color-2">Introduction</font></h2>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h2_p">
                Owlybook is a collection of stories that showcase many component available in the Odoo software.
                Whether you're new to Odoo or a seasoned user, Owlybook is a great way to discover and explore.
                <br/>
                In here, you will have the possibility to see, try and play with a lot of different component and architecture
                available to you by the Odoo software.
            </p>

            <h2><font class="text-o-color-2">What is Owlybook ?</font></h2>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h2_p">
                Owlybook is composed of different distinct element that we will explain in the next section. To be precise,
                it is composed of three elements (Sidebar, canvas and bottom panel).
            </p>
            <h3><font class="text-o-color-1 ms-5">Sidebar</font></h3>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-5 ps-5">Stories</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                In the context of Owlybook, a "story" is a term used to refer to a single instance of a UI component with
                a set of defined inputs, props or a specific state. It allows developers to create and display variations
                of a component in isolation, and document their behavior and functionality. Each story is a self-contained entity
                that showcases a specific use case of the component, making it easier for developers to test, debug, and collaborate
                on the development of UI components.
                <br/>
                You can see on the sidebar that our Owlybook has multiple stories organised into a sort of file explorer.
                Each folder can be close or open, and selecting a story on the sidebar will display on the canvas the according story.
            </p>

            <h3><font class="text-o-color-1 ms-5">Canvas</font></h3>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Component</font></h4>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Arch</font></h4>

            <h3><font class="text-o-color-1 ms-5">Bottom Panel</font></h3>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Props</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                This page is maybe the most important one of the bottom panel, since it allow you to play with props of the component or arch field.
                Modifying lines in the props panel should modify the story in real time.
            </p>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Events</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                In the bottom panel, you will be able to see (for some specific stories) a page named "Events".
                This page will show you the different actions done on the stories you are playing with. Be careful that those events are volatile.
                When changing stories, you will lose your events.
            </p>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Code</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                This page is displayed only if the stories is using an arch. It's pretty straightforward as you will be able
                to see the code of the arch so that you can copy and paste it for your personal use.
            </p>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">JavaScript</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                This page is displayed only if the stories is using a component. In this section you will be able to see the JavaScript code.
                Modifying the code in the editor below will not modify the component. Its purpose is to copy/paste or to understand the component usage.
            </p>
            <h4><font class="text-o-color-2 ms-10">Template</font></h4>
            <p class="o_owlybook_h4_p">
                This page is displayed only if the stories is using a component. Same as the javascript code,
                except that here you will be able to see the template.
            </p>

        </div>
    </t>
</templates>
